This is Lucia.
She is getting ready to start her wrestling season.
She remembers that last season she felt tired
all the time and struggled to make weight.
This season,
her goal is to eat smarter and manage her weight more effectively.
She needs to make the right decisions in order to be on weight but still strong.
Oh no,
I'm 3 pounds heavier.
Will I be able to make weight for my competition in a few days?
I remember hearing my teammates talk about skipping
meals or wearing sweatsuits to drop weight.
I could try that,
but is it safe?
Lucia reflects on what she just learned about the differences between
cutting and fueling and how risky cutting weight can be.
She wonders if there is a better way to handle this situation.